"Does my bum look big in this?"
“我穿这个屁股看起来很大吗？”
That's what I asked myself when I tried on the designer jeans I bought in the Christmas sales and the mirror... well, the mirror didn't actually say anything but I got the message: It's time to go on a diet!
这是我在试穿圣诞节促销时买的设计师牛仔裤时问自己的问题，而镜子……嗯，镜子实际上什么都没说，但我明白了：是时候开始节食了！
Sometimes we just don't know how many calories we eat.
有时我们完全不知道自己摄入了多少卡路里。
Experts say cooking meals from scratch can help you think about the ingredients which go into your food.
专家表示，从头开始烹饪可以帮助你思考食物中的食材。
Tam Fry, from the UK's National Obesity Forum, says: "Learning how to cook fresh food is really the number one thing to consider when tackling obesity and improving weight loss."
英国国家肥胖论坛的塔姆·弗莱说：“学习如何烹饪新鲜食物确实是应对肥胖和改善减肥效果时需要考虑的首要事情。”
If you can't cook, Fry recommends that you be more aware of what you put in your trolley when you go to the supermarket.
如果你不会做饭，弗莱建议你在去超市时要更加注意你放进购物车的东西。
He points out: "People don't read food labels.
他指出：“人们不阅读食品标签。
At government level making the labels easier to read and understand is key, but just looking at how many grams of sugar is in something is really important."
在政府层面，使标签更容易阅读和理解是关键，但仅仅查看某物中有多少克糖就已经十分重要了。”
Some experts believe that a good way to reduce your waistline might be to start by reducing the size of the plate you eat from.
一些专家认为，让腰围瘦下来的一个好方法可能是从缩小你吃饭的盘子开始。
Research has suggested that people eat most of what they serve themselves, so big portions lead to overeating.
研究表明，人们会吃掉他们自己盛的大部分食物，所以大份量会导致过量饮食。
A study by Dr Brian Wansink, from Cornell University, US, claimed that reducing plate size from about 30cm to 25cm typically results in 22% fewer calories being served, as the smaller plate makes a normal serving seem more filling.
美国康奈尔大学的布莱恩·万辛克博士的一项研究声称，将盘子尺寸从约30厘米减少到25厘米通常会导致饮食中所提供的卡路里减少22%，因为较小的盘子使正常份量看起来更饱。
However, once plate size went below about 24cm, "people begin to realise they're tricking themselves and go back for seconds and thirds".
然而，一旦盘子尺寸低于约24厘米，“人们开始意识到他们在欺骗自己，并会回去盛第二份和第三份”。
I think I'll keep my current plates for now.
我想我会暂时保留我现在的盘子。
As for me, nothing beats an inspiring image on the fridge door - a picture of my lovely jeans - with some wise quote as a caption.
至于我，没有什么比冰箱门上的一张鼓舞人心的图片——我那条迷人牛仔裤的照片——加上一些充满智慧的引语作为标题更好的了。
As supermodel Kate Moss once said: "Nothing tastes as good as skinny feels."
正如超模凯特·莫斯曾经说过的：“没有什么比苗条的感觉更好。”
No more big bum for me!
我再也不要大屁股了！